http://www.dordt.edu/privacy-policy

Jump to navigation
Dordt’s COVID-19 alert level is YELLOW. Face masks are required.
FAQ
How is the Amount Calculated?
KDCR
Marketing and CommunicationBrand & Media ResourcesFaculty Experts
Our Donors
BACKGROUNDAffiliated Academic CentersAndreas CenterAbout Lowell Andreas
K and K Dooyema Center for Entrepreneurship and Innovation
Kielstra Center for Research and GrantsInstitutional Review BoardOnline Research Proposal Form
External Scholarly Recognitions
Statistical Genetics and BiostatisticsApplication Information
University InitiativeFAQs
AcademicsDEGREE OPTIONSUndergraduate degreesAssociate's DegreesAdministrative AssistantOutcomesAlumni Employment
Outcomes
Theatre FestivalApplication for High School Theatre Festival
Undecided Resources
Graduate degreesMaster of Education ProgramAdmission Requirements
Off-Campus StudyApplication Process
Approved Semester ProgramsDordt Semester ProgramsSPICEApply NowHousing Form
Useful Links
Online CoursesDual Credit CoursesDual Credit Online Application
Study Skills Assistance
Support Services For Students With DisabilitiesAccessibility For Students With Disabilities
Library
Admissions & AidFIND OUT MORESchedule a Campus VisitCampus Visit Bus/Plane Trip Payment
Find my admissions counselor
What is the college decision process?
Helpful Links
How Do I Apply?
DO MORE at Dordt
Student LifeCHRIST CENTEREDCampus MinistriesAll Campus Retreat
Chapel
Service opportunitiesA Mission OutReach (AMOR)
Community Outreach Program (COP)
Putting Love Into Action (PLIA)
CAMPUS LIFEArts
Clubs
Get to Know CampusParking Map
Student Activities
RESIDENCE LIFEStudent Health and Counseling CenterMedical Services
Privacy Policy and Terms of Use
Last updated and reviewed on November 21, 2019.
Dordt values privacy because we value you; your privacy is important to Dordt. This statement provides insights into what information we collect, how the information is used, and other additional items related to protecting your privacy.
You may view, copy, print, and use content provided on Dordt's website for your own personal use and provided that:
The website's content is used for informational and non-commercial purposes only;
No text, graphics, or other content available from this website are modified in any way; and
No website graphics are used, copied, or distributed separately from the accompanying text.
The Dordt logo may not be used in any electronic or printed publications without permission from Dordt's Marketing and Communication Office. Please contact marcomm@dordt.edu for additional details.
The Dordt website contains links to other websites on the Internet; we are not responsible for the content or privacy policies of these sites. Reference herein to any specific products, process, publication, or service does not necessarily constitute or imply an endorsement by Dordt.
To maintain the uniformity and integrity of this website, any Dordt departments or programs that wish to have independent pages on the website must be approved on a case-by-case basis. Contact marcomm@dordt.edu for more information.
Information Collection and Use
Dordt collects information to better personalize your website experience. The college automatically collects certain pieces of information, including your IP address, your Internet service provider, your time on the website, and navigation path on the website using Google Analytics. We use this information to provide you with the best possible information service. Other information that Dordt collects includes demographic and geographic information from Google Analytics.
Dordt also uses Pardot, a marketing automation tool. Pardot sets cookies, tiny files that are downloaded to your computer, for tracking purposes and sets third-party cookies for redundancy. Using first-party and third-party cookies together is standard in the marketing automation industry. Pardot cookies do not store personally identifying information, they store only a unique identifier. Pardot tracks visitor and prospect activities on this website and on Pardot landing pages by setting cookies. These cookies are set in order to remember preferences (like form field values) when a visitor returns to this site, and again to provide you with the best possible information service.
Dordt uses remarketing and other online advertising means to better reach our online audiences. The college uses third-party vendors, including Google, to show ads on sites across the Internet. To opt out of Google's use of cookies, please visit Google's Ads Settings. Also, if you would like to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies, please visit the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page. Please note that disabling cookies will affect the functionality of this and many other websites that you visit. It is our recommendation that you do not disable cookies.
Your information is for internal use only. Dordt may share some of the information collected with contracted third-party vendors, companies who are acting on our behalf, or jointly with Dordt, under a contractual arrangement when necessary to fulfill the services of Dordt. We may also share information when required to do so by law.
Whenever possible, we do not share information with third-party vendors unless they have agreed in writing to provide the same level of privacy protection as provided by Dordt.
We do not disclose private information about you for the purposes of marketing or soliciting products or services other than our own.
E-Commerce
Some of our website features may use applications to collect data to facilitate an e-commerce transaction. In this case, we use third-party vendors with an approved banking relationship to process credit card transactions. All credit card information is encrypted and only the information needed to complete transaction history is stored on secure servers.
Commercial
Dordt may use your personal information to contact you via email or by postal mail with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials. The input of that information is voluntary. To update your records, please use this form or contact alumni@dordt.edu.
Security
Information submitted on this website is maintained on a private secure server and is handled in a confidential manner.
Other Links
The Dordt website may contain destination links to other websites including Dordt student groups, third-party organizations outside of the “dordt.edu” domain, and more. Dordt is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such websites. These destination links are provided only for your convenience, and as such, you access them at your own risk. Any information you reveal on any such site is not subject to this privacy statement; therefore, you should consult the privacy policies of each site you visit. However, we wish to ensure the integrity of our website and its destination links, so any comments pertaining to any sites accessed through destination links on our website are greatly appreciated. Please contact us at website@dordt.edu.
Privacy Statement Changes
Dordt may change this privacy statement at any time by posting revisions to our website. Your use of the website constitutes acceptance of the most current privacy statement. If you do not agree to the terms of the privacy statement, then please exit and discontinue use of the website immediately.
Surveys
From time to time, this website requests that website users participate in the sharing of information via survey. Filling out the survey is completely voluntary. Some of the information requested may include contact information and other relevant information.
Social Media Accounts
Our social media pages are for supporters of Dordt University, and we encourage open discussion on the following platforms: Facebook, Instagram, LinkedIn, Twitter, & YouTube. By participating on/with our pages, you are agreeing to our commenting policy, outlined below.
We reserve the right to delete comments or posts on our page containing any of the following elements:
promoting activity contrary to the student handbook or Dordt's Educational Task & Framework.
If you repeatedly violate this policy, your comments will be deleted, and you will be removed from our page.
With any questions regarding our social media accounts or this policy, you can email us at marcomm@dordt.edu.
Recent Alumni ($50)
White Level ($100)
Black Level ($250)
Silver Level ($500)
Gold Level ($1,000)
Diamond Level ($2,000)
Club Level ($5,000)
Defender Level ($10,000)
Recent Alumni ($50)
White Level ($100)
Black Level ($250)
Sorry, we couldn't find any giving options for the selected designation.
Silver Level ($500)
Gold Level ($1,000)
Diamond Level ($2,000)
Club Level ($5,000)
Defender Level ($10,000)
Waiting for product selection.
Looking for more information about giving opportunities? Click here.
